{
    "id": "523aaa0b5f1842229c38a6cd98dfaac1",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She isn’t coming, ......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mary has arrived, .....................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has she",
                "hasn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He eats too much, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You should obey the rules, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should you",
                "shouldn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is here, .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is he",
                "isn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He works hard, .....................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I hurt you, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am I",
                "didn't I",
                "did I"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You have finished, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "haven't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He often comes late, .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go for a walk, ......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall we",
                "should we",
                "may we"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}